Welcome to the ZeroClaw shop.
Um, this is a Brazilian or Portuguese
native shop.
I asked the agent to make a payment.
I want to make a payment of two reais.
As you can notice, it's typing.
By the way, this is a demo for the
ZeroClaw and Superteam BR bounty.
So it, it responded and if you notice at
the bottom of...
Besides the link it gave for the payment
page, it's also smart that it converts
the requested amount I asked in Brazilian
currency to USD.
It knows the exchange rate.
Okay, we've now opened the payment link in
the browser, and here we have
a Solana Pay QR code. But before we scan
it,
like, take a look at, at this.
This is a terminal that's monitoring for
transaction, and this is the same
link opened in, in the browser on desktop.
More about this in a second.
So back here, let's scan the QR code.
Then approve payment in Solflare.
Okay, transaction successful on mainnet.
Let's see it on the Explorer.
Okay, nice. Now... Oh, I came back too
late.
And also notice this,
it automatically detected the transaction
both-- on both sides, the terminal
and the page, the same payment link.
And if you click here, you go to the same
Explorer.
That's it for the demo. Thank you.